Craig Seymour Collection, 1968-2006 SC 144
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 4. Interviews
  - 4.25. Miscellaneous interviews for articles
    - Joe Nichols, 1 Audiocassette; Joe Nichols (country music artist) discussing his song "The Impossible," country music, etc.
    - Jonathan Taylor Thomas, 2000?; 1 Audiocassette; Discusses his role in Common Ground, a made for TV movie about homosexuality.
      cass 2066 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/118r371n4n
    - Kandi Burruss, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about her solo album Hey Kandi (2000), her work with TLC and Destiny's Child.
      cass 2076 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d37584002v
    - Kelly Price, 2 Audiocassettes; Telephone interview with R&B singer Price about her work, women in hip hop, her background in the Church of God in Christ, her work with Mariah Carey, etc. for a feature interview in the Washington Post.
      cass 2081 A/B, cass 2105 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h04d67237j
    - Kevin "She'kspere" Briggs [?], 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about his work with NSYNC and other artists.
    - Laurie [?], 1 Audiocassette; Calling about art for article on Darius [?]
    - Lee Ann Womack, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview about her Something Worth Leaving Behind album (2002).
    - Manfred Jones, circa February 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with singer and Wuxtry Records employee discussing the death of Waylon Jennings.
      cass 2083 A
    - Mark Wright, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Mark Wright (producer for Lee Ann Womack) on Womack's 2002 album Something Worth Leaving Behind, song choice, etc.
    - Natalie Maines, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about her personal life and the Dixie Chicks.
    - Nelly, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about touring and his recent chart successes.
      cass 2113 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k12831jv22
    - Neptunes (Pharrell Williams, Chad Hugo), 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with Hugo and Williams on their work, webcasting recording sessions, awards, etc.
      cass 2066 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/5547725v9d
    - Nikolas Ashford and Valerie Simpson, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with songwriters Ashford & Simpson discussing love songs, their work, Chaka Khan, Marvin Gaye, etc.
    - Dr. Pat Turner, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Dr. Pat Turner (UC Davis) discussing Elvis and race relations, other racial incidents in US cultural history.
    - Patti Austin, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interviews with about jazz and her upcoming concert in Atlanta.
      cass 2154 A/B
    - Pete Rock, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Pete Rock (of Pete Rock & CL Smooth) about the album Mecca and the Soul Brother.
      cass 2086 B
    - R. Kelly, circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Interview in advance of the release of his album TP-2.com.
      cass 2070 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h73p88jz7v
    - Regina Belle, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview discussing her leaving MCA and her recent work.
    - Rich [Harrison?], 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview discussing his work with Amerie and Mary J. Blige.
      cass 2113 A
    - Rick James, 2001?; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about his album Street Songs, the release of the Deluxe Edition.
      cass 2068 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p68k424v35
    - Rupaul (RuPaul Andre Charles), 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Rupaul on hip hop, her work, etc.
      cass 2116 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/445c38cn4r
    - Sandra Bernhard, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Bernhard (comedian/vocalist) discussing an upcoming show, probably in Atlanta in late 2001 or 2002.
      cass 2137 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n99920n915
    - Shyne [Jamal Barrow], 1 Audiocassette; Interview about his debut album and Bad Boy Records, probably conducted in 2000 or early 2001.
      cass 2076 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d66v936b1k
    - Stu Maschwitz, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Stu Maschwitz (co-founder of The Orphanage, a visual effects company) about Cher's "Song for the Lonely" video and Living Proof (2002) album.
    - Tommy Mottola, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview about Ricky Martin, the then-new Michael Jackson album (Invincible), other new releases in 2001, press coverage of Sony.
      cass 2100 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j82k22bd4c
    - Tweet, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about her recent single "Oops (Oh My!)."
    - Usher, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Usher discussing his Grammy nomination, album sales, his music.
    - Usher, 2001-09; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Usher about his work, the state of R&B.
      cass 2104 A
    - Violet [?], 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Violet, Director of Urban Music at unknown organization, about R&B.
    - Unidentified person, 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Interview with unidentified man about someone getting stabbed at the Source Awards in Pasadena, CA - names mentioned in this interview may be sensitive: Seymour agrees not to use them in an article.
      cass 2063 A
    - Unidentified person discussing techno music, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with unidentified musician discussing the state and trajectory of techno music.
    - Unidentified businesswoman, 1 Audiocassette; Discussing African-Americans breaking into the country music industry.
    - Unidentified singer, 1 Audiocassette; Discusses her experiences as an African American country singer in Nashville.
    - Seymour voicemail, 1 Audiocassette; Seymour leaves a voicemail for Ty [?].
    - Unidentified record industry person, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about music from the 80s on catalog charts.
    - Unidentified member of R.E.M., 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about the album packaging for R.E.M.'s Reveal.
  - Categorized interview questions index cards, undated; 1 Folder (Box 7, Folder 19)
- 5. Audiovisual (excluding interviews)
  - 5.1. Mixtapes and miscellaneous media
    - D.J. Mandrill - Clubhouse Live Mixtape [Pete?], 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2440
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s55m317367
    - D.J. Mandrill - Dance Music Mixtape, 1988-07; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2441
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/445c38cn6c
    - D.J. Mandrill - Blactracks Mixtape [Pete?], 1989; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2442
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/930b88wp58
    - D.J. Mandrill - Ritz House Deep Mixtape, 1992-10; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2443
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/494v53rj5c
    - D.J. Mandrill - Tracks Live Mixtape [Craig?], 1992-11; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2444
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n59q08bx66
    - D.J. Mandrill - Ritz House Mixtape [Craig?], 1993-02; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2445
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c67w62mj65
    - D.J. Mandrill - Ritz House Mixtape, 1993-03-20; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2446
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/217q67r00j
    - D.J. Mandrill - Lantern Live 988 - 1 Mixtape, 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2447
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p88c488n8k
    - D.J. Mandrill - Housin Sum 99-1 (Soulful Mix) Mixtape [Drill Impulse Productions], 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2449
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v73b98sn76
    - D.J. Mandrill - Hallelujah House Mix IV Mixtape [Drill Impulse Productions], 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2450
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f95j338d8n
    - D.J. Mandrill - Pardy Hardy VI Mixtape [Drill Impulse Productions], 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2451
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/207t64nv8x
    - D.J. Mandrill [Drill Impulse Records] [Side A Only], 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2452
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/890r76mk0d
    - Lil Mo Album Snippets, 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2453
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/643999tb2m
    - Radioscope; WPGC 95.5 aircheck, 1997?; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2454
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g74q57qq69
    - Jerome Hicks - Live at Paradox, 1993-04-03; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2455
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d56z908b3d
    - DJ Clue Radio Broadcast - Monday Night Mixtape, Hot 97 [WQHT 97.1 FM], 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2456
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f26811rr49
    - Others Viewing Others: The Representation of Gender and Sexuality [Tape 2], 1991?; 1 Audiocassette
      cass 2457
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/445c38cn7p
    - Rare Mary J. Blige tracks + Interviews on Angie Martinez Show, 1997-04-2000-05-30; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 68
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/445c388c82
    - DJ Juice - Mary J Blige: Da Past, Da Present, Da Future, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 192
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n30099184z
    - Felix Da Housecat - Excursions (Title from Amazon), 2002; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 193
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/247d76tx4n
    - DJ Drama and Pharrell - In My Mind (The Prequel) plus 5 extra tracks (Title from Amazon), circa 2006; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 194
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z80593x23c
    - Lalah Hathaway - Outrun the Sky, 2004-09-21; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 195
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j23603sz11
    - DJ Ayres / The Rub - It's the Motherfucking Remix, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 196
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z20s75gh8h
    - DJ Clue presents Hev.E. Components Part 1: William M. Holla, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 197
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h04d66xx6p
    - Back to Mine: New Order (multiple DJ mixtape series), 2002-11-05; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 198
    - Tony Touch (AKA the Piece Maker) - Deeper House Mix #35, 2004-02-24; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 199
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/f55z20vr55
    - Bootrax - 13+10+01, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 200
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t05346g81k
    - DJ Roli Fingaz - Fire Blends 7, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 201
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/q47r66m84t
    - The Pulling Strings Mixtape (various DJs with violinist Miri Ben-Ari), 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 202
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r36t94818z
    - DJ Neil Armstrong - Bittersweet, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 203
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r96712p765
    - Dress Shirt Mafia - Volume 1: Grown & Sexy Takeover (hosted by Brucie B), 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 204
    - Big Mike - R&B Jumpoff Part 6, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 205
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/m214657h09
    - Soca Gold - Cropover Musical Mix Pt. 6, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 206
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j82k227b71
    - For My Fam's On Lock Down - C-74 Ready for War!, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 207
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/821g550m5v
    - The Warriors - New Years Resolution (hosted by Brucie B.), 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 208
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/178455bc8q
    - Hot 97 - Request Line Volume 3, 2005-08-02; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 209
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d27880xt72
    - Tapemasters Inc - Future of R&B Pt. 6, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 210
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h343765c35
    - DJ Drama & Young Jeezy - Can't Ban the Snowman, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 211
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c97k71qk35
    - DJ Mandrill - The Deep End Live: A Luther Vandross Feelin 1, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 212
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b09j13c045
    - DJ Mandrill - The Deep End: A "Diana Ross" Feelin 1, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 213
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k71n500p4d
    - DJ Mandrill - The Deep End: A "Diana Ross" Feelin 2, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 214
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t74c67zw4w
    - DJ Mandrill - The Deep End Live: A Luther Vandross Feelin 2, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 215
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k41z40p28c
    - DJ Mandrill - The Deep End Live: A Luther Vandross Feelin 3, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 216
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s35t24zs31
    - DJ Mandrill - The Deep End: A "India Feelin" Live 3, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 217
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/791s45sf00
    - DJ Mandrill - The Deep End Live: A Sylvester Feelin 1, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 218
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/742930dz03
    - DJ Mandrill - Live from the Deep End: Chaka Khan Fever 2, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 219
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/178455bc91
    - Kanye West & Clinton Sparks, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 220
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/930b88sb4g
    - Chaka Khan (untitled, 10 tracks), 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 221
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/227m70pt49
    - Jay Jannan - Lazy Dog, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 222
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j52w131639
    - Byron Stingily - Club Stories, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 223
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/9601980q6q
    - Chops & Kanye West - Changing Lanes (Mixed by DJ Lt. Dan), 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 224
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/q085549v75
    - Craig's Random Dance Stuff, CD 1, 2001-06; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 225
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/m117625h25
    - Newshit: 19 July 00 Vol 1, 2000-07-19; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 226
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p58p38zh6j
    - Luther Vandross - Luther, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 227
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x21t44rt73
    - Soiree & Revelation: Get In Touch, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 228
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/890r76h85r
    - Luther Vandross, 2001-05-27; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 229
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r66j03g55x
    - "Bustin' Loose" Soundtrack; Miscellaneous Luther background vocals, 1979-1981; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 230
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g84m60ss2g
    - Mascara & Luther Mixes, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 231
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/544b690c33
    - Luther, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 232
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c67w62h867
    - Step Aside for a Lady; Miscellaneous Luther background vocals, 1973-1980; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 233
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r66j03g567
    - The Luther Era V1.1, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 234
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d56z90551p
    - Live, 2003-09-19; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 235
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t44p58rq5f
    - Miller Sound Experience Concert Hour, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 236
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/593t84bj7m
    - Dance With My Father, 2003-03-03; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 237
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d472873007
    - Amerie, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 587
    - Twista - Chopped + Screwed, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 588
    - Hot Property, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 589
    - Sammi Smith, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 590
    - Femi Kuti - Shoki Remixed, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 591
    - tahiti80plus, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 592
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 593
    - Beats, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 594
    - Dionne Warwick, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 595
    - Love's Arrival - Larry Heard, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 596
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 597
    - Craig, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 598
    - Atlanta Dancing: I, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 599
    - Untilited, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 600
    - Untitled, 2000-03-12; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 601
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 602
    - Napster 1/10, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 603
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 604
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 605
    - Down to Earth, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 606
    - Jams, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 607
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 608
    - Untitled, 1999-05-17; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 609
    - jill, syleena, george, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 610
    - takin' over like Francis (you forgot?), 2000-02-20-2000-02-21; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 611
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 612
    - Seth 2004 Birthday Ol' School Jams!!!, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 613
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 614
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 615
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 616
    - Delores Hall, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 617
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 618
    - untitled playlist, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 619
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 620
    - all the way live, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 621
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 622
    - Ms. Dynamite, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 623
    - Kelly Price - Priceless, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 624
    - Shanice - every woman dreams, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 625
    - mica, justin, 50 cent, lil' kim, swisha house, j-lo, xtina, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 626
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 627
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 628
    - Mostly Mix Tape Shit, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 629
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 630
    - Selections, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 631
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 632
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 633
    - Misc Stuff, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 634
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 635
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 636
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 637
    - Recloose, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 638
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 639
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 640
    - Tony Toca +, 2000-07-31; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 641
    - gym shit, week of 6/1, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 642
    - DJ hell, Cassius Mandalay, gus gus, timo + kelis, underworld, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 643
    - Monica - Inside, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 644
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 645
    - Mary & Aaliyah, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 646
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 647
    - Mary J. Blige - Give Me You + More, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 648
    - Dance Mix, 2000-03-09; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 649
    - Two Step R&B, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 650
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 651
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 652
    - Not Just Talkin' It, 2000-09-11; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 653
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 654
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 655
    - Club, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 656
    - Remixes, 2000-12; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 657
    - well all right, you freaks...this is for the grown & sexy, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 658
    - HMS10, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 659
    - 1st choice, tiga, jean-jacques, Bushwacka! & more, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 660
    - Michael Remixed, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 661
    - DJL Satisfaction Guaranteed Mixtape, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 662
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 663
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 664
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 665
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 666
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 667
    - Hip Hop NYC - your child, etc., 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 668
    - Joi, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 669
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 670
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 671
    - Bionic Boogie, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 672
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 673
    - Brandy + Monica v. Modjo, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 674
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 675
    - Blu Cantrell - Arista Sampler, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 676
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 677
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 678
    - Foxy Brown - Fever Warm Up, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 679
    - jaheimandmore, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 680
    - Mix CD, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 681
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 682
    - Act Like You Mo, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 683
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 684
    - Mess Up, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 685
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 686
    - a seth CD, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 687
    - Untitled, 2006-05-17; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 688
    - Untitled, 2006-02-04; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 689
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 690
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 691
    - Monica...A First Listen, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 692
    - Seth House CD, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 693
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 694
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 695
    - Craig's Best of Aaliyah, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 696
    - Kim +, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 697
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 698
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 699
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 700
    - Mystikal, Common, & Changing Faces, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 701
    - House Stuff 6/01, 2001-06; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 702
    - Untitled, 2006-05-18; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 703
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 704
    - seth7oct, 2005-10-07; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 705
    - seth11dec, 2005-12-11; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 706
    - seth20oct, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 707
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 708
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 709
    - bootleg/from the archive, 2000-09-28; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 710
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 711
    - missy teary eyes plus, 2006-02-01; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 712
    - seth23jan, 2006-01-23; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 713
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 714
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 715
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 716
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 717
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 718
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 719
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 720
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 721
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 722
    - CraigOctober14b, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 723
    - 6aprilseth, 2006-04-06; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 724
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 725
    - Screwed Jams, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 726
    - Screwed Ballads, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 727
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 728
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 729
    - 3Nov, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 730
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 731
    - Memphis Bleek - More from Disappearing Acts..., 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 732
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 733
    - Pilote - Antenna; Photek - "Something else...the Bleeps Tune", 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 734
    - New York in August, Volume I, 1999-08-09; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 735
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 736
    - Pop Sampler #1, 1999-09-27; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 737
    - Pop Sampler #2, 1999-09; 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 738
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 739
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 740
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 741
    - Untitled, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 742
    - Herbert - Bodily Functions, 1 Audio Disc CD-R
      CDR 743